Hi.
I'm Jason Mac Genius and today we're going to talk about finding wireless internet.
If you have an Apple lap top this is what you need to do to find wireless internet.
Open it.
That's as easy as that.
That's really all you have to do.
So, in finding wireless internet if you don't have an airport icon up here in your menu bar I'm going to show you a quick little tip that you can get that up there.
We're going to go to system preferences, network and we've got airport selected here.
We're going to go show airport and show status in menu bar.
So, now you see you've got a little airport up here.
I always like to show everything in the menu bar that way you know, if you've got a whole line of icons up at the top you're super cool.
So, we click on our airport and we've got multiple networks up here that we can choose from.
Pretty much any time you open your lap top lid you're going to get an automatic scan; airport is going to go and find every wireless network it can and give you an option to connect to it.
If there is a little lock icon over in the corner of it that means you need a password to get into it and if you don't have the password you're out of luck.
So, we're going to connect to Linux and that's pretty much it.
I'm Jason MacGenus and it's as easy as that connecting to a network.
Take care.